var questionsObj = {
  quizName : "Demo Quiz III",
  quizTags : ["Demo"],
  startTime : 1540933200000,
  questionCount : 10,
  questions: [
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 11',
      question: 'Where is India\'s first Uranium mine located?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Jadugoda',
        option2: 'Palakkad',
        option3: 'Sriharikota',
        option4: 'Dalbhum'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Jadugoda'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 12',
      question: 'Bituminous and Anthracite are types of _______',
      options: {
        option1: 'Diamond',
        option2: 'Bauxite',
        option3: 'Coal',
        option4: 'Radium'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Coal'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 13',
      question: 'Who is the author of "Mein Kampf"?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Karl Marx',
        option2: 'Napolean Bonaparte',
        option3: 'Benito Mussolini',
        option4: 'Adolf Hitler'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Adolf Hitler'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 14',
      question: 'Which of this is NOT a book written by Jawahar Lal Nehru?',
      options: {
        option1: 'The Discovery of India',
        option2: 'Letters from a Father to his Daughter',
        option3: 'India of My dreams',
        option4: 'Glimpses of World History'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'India of My Dreams'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 15',
      question: 'Who was the first Indian Nobel Laureate?',
      options: {
        option1: 'Rabindranath Tagore',
        option2: 'C.V Raman',
        option3: 'Mother Teresa',
        option4: 'Amartya Sen'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Rabindranath Tagore'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 11',
      question: 'Rajat points to a picture and says " He is the son of the only son of my Mother." How is he related to the boy in the picture',
      options: {
        option1: 'Brother',
        option2: 'Uncle',
        option3: 'Father',
        option4: 'Cousin'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'Father'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 12',
      question: 'Unscramble the following letters to make a dictionary word : SASAITNOICO',
      options: {
        option1: 'ASSASSINATION',
        option2: 'ASSOCIATION',
        option3: 'UNCERTAINTY',
        option4: 'CONSOLATION'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'ASSOCIATION'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 13',
      question: 'If you have South to your Left, and you throw a stone towards your back, which direction did you throw the stone in?',
      options: {
        option1: 'West',
        option2: 'North',
        option3: 'East',
        option4: 'South'
      },
      correctAnswer: 'East'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 14',
      question: '123 x 456',
      options: {
        option1: '10,018',
        option2: '56,088',
        option3: '54,684',
        option4: '58,632'
      },
      correctAnswer: '56,088'
    },
    {
      questionNumber: 'Question 15',
      question: 'The multiplication product of all the numbers on a phone keypad is equal to ____',
      options: {
        option1: '3,62,880',
        option2: '3,56,795',
        option3: '3,64,552',
        option4: '0'
      },
      correctAnswer: '0'
    }
  ]}

  module.exports.quizQuestions = questionsObj;